GABRIEL CARVALHO COSTA

CONTACT

Rua Capitão Anselmo, 1960, Franca, São Paulo 14401-154 Brazil

\$ 5516991854437

☑ gabrielcarvalhocosta@live.com

in <u>linkedin.com/in/gabriel-carvalho-costa/</u>

github.com/gabriel-Oak

SKILLS

- Problem-solving
- Unity Tests
- ReactJS
- NextJSAngular 2+
- React Native
- Flutter
- Node.JS
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- RedisAWS
- TDD
- 100
- Clean Architecture
- · Good coding practicies
- Scrum
- Kamban
- Micro-services

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I've been working with systems development for over 4 years and I'm passionate about what I do. I started programming at the age of 13, so I can safely say that coding occupies most of my life.

I always seek to deliver with quality, automated tests and clean architecture, even if I don't use the clean arch itself. I'm communicative and I try to clear up doubts before starting to develop a feature, I need to be sure of what the end user expects to receive, or discover together with him.

I recently worked leading projects and my team, delegating tasks and supporting other devs as needed. Whenever I can, I try to share knowledge and train my teammates, in order to achieve an even greater collective result

I like to know that what I do changes people's lives, well-used technology has the power to revolutionize the market, societies and change lives just as it changed mine.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

April 2020 - Current

Mobile Developer Freelancer

So far I work as a freelancer with flutter and react native, developing tailor-made solutions for the customer.

CVC Corp | Santo André, SP, Brazil

April 2021 - January 2023

Full Stack Developer

I worked on the development of the website for selling airline tickets at CVC Corp, one of the biggest tour companies in latin america. I led the team in the migration project of our old legacy BFF in .NET to a brand new Node.JS app, implementing clean architecture, delegating tasks, test driven development, mandatory code review and supporting juniors devs through pair programming. Also made a new ReactJS clean arch based architecture and raised stories(tasks) for the the migration project.

LojaDoMecanico (GurgelMix) | Franca, SP, Brazil

April 2020 - April 2021

Full Stack Developer

I worked on intranet development in node and reactjs. I developed the POS portal for sellers, responsible for 20% of the company's revenue, in a Reacjs microfrontend integrating with another php frontend.

MazzaFC | Franca, SP, Brazil

January 2020 - April 2020

Full Stack Developer

I worked on the development of an ERP for carriers using node micro services, with postgresql database. Integrating with frontend in ReactJS and React Native.

SMN Technologia | Franca, SP, Brazil

March 2019 - January 2020

Front End Developer

I worked on migrating a legacy asp project to angular 8.

EDUCATION

July 2020

Technologist - System Development

Fatec Dr. Thomaz Novelino, Franca, SP, Brazil

December 2016

High School Diploma

Etec Dr. Julio Cardoso, Franca, SP, Brazil

LANGUAGES

Portuguese English Spanish
Native Advanced Conversational

HOBBIES

I love to go camping and hiking in the wild Also love to climb at the gym or in the nature